domai.nr 2019-05-27

# Privacy Policy · Domainr

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Domainr collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Domainr’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how visitors use the domainr.com service. From time to time, Domainr may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its service.

Domainr also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Domainr has a legitimate interest in collecting potentially personally identifying information; the purpose being to provide and improve the service, to keep the service safe and secure, and to protect the service from abuse. Domainr only discloses IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses potentially personally-identifying information as described below.

We may determine the approximate location of users’ web browsers from their IP addresses. We collect and use this information to, for example, calculate how many people visit Domainr from certain geographic regions, and to recommend relevant domain names for a given geographic region.

## Protection of Certain Potentially Personally-Identifying Information

Domainr discloses potentially personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Domainr’s behalf, or to provide services available via the Domainr service, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Domainr service, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Domainr will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, Domainr discloses potentially personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order, or other governmental request, or when Domainr believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Domainr, third parties, or the public at large.

Domainr reserves the right to disclose potentially personally identifying information and/or non-personally-identifiable information to assist government enforcement agencies, and to protect the security and integrity of our services. Domainr takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying information.

## Information Security

Domainr has multiple procedures in place to help safeguard, prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use potentially personally-identifying and non‑personal information. These procedures include using unique, per-service strong passwords for service provider accounts, and multi-factor authentication methods. Although we strive to employ reasonable protections for potentially personally-identifiable information that are appropriate to its sensitivity, we do not guarantee or warrant the security of this information. No system is 100% secure.

Data breaches: Where a breach occurs, Domainr shall, upon discovering such a breach, ensure that our obligations are met under applicable data privacy requirements, and with specific acknowledgement of Articles 33 and 34 of the GDPR, where applicable.

Data retention: Domainr does not retain any potentially personally-identifying information for longer than is necessary to provide the services to you and others, to detect and research abusive client behavior, subject to any legal obligations to further retain such information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Domainr may use cookies to help Domainr identify and track visitors, their usage of the Domainr service, and their website access preferences. Domainr visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Domainr service.

## Affiliate Programs

Affiliate Program links appearing on the Domainr service may be delivered to users by affiliate network providers, which may set cookies. These cookies allow affiliate providers to recognize your web browser each time you visit one of our partner sites, in order to track Domainr’s commissions for referring sales on these partner sites. (For example, domain name purchases at our partner registrar and reseller sites.) This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Domainr and does not cover the use of cookies by any affiliate network provider. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our website, and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by Domainr.

## Business Transfers

If Domainr, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Domainr goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Domainr may continue to use your potentially personally-identifying information as set forth in this policy.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Domainr may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Domainr’s sole discretion. Domainr encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this service after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

_Privacy Policy text courtesy of[Automattic](https://github.com/Automattic/legalmattic)._

_Last updated: May 24, 2018_
